ABISOLA IFEOLUWA AWOSEMO

73, Temidire Estate, Off Ajia road, Iyana Agbala, New Ife road, Egbeda, Ibadan.

Telephone: +2347030458845

E-mail: abisolaawosemo@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

Chartered Accountant (in-view), with experience in Financial Accounting, Taxation, Auditing and an extensive knowledge in Management. Detailed-oriented, efficient, organized, and personable. Possesses an excellent written and verbal communication skill, strong Analytical and problem solving skills, with an exquisite ability to make well thought-out decisions. A good team player who advocates for integrity, trustworthiness, accuracy and practices ethical-professionalism. Resourceful in completion of project while aiding the achievement of organisational goals and objectives.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BOLDFORM CONSULTS, IBADAN

Oyo-State

Position: Business Executive

Jan, 2020-March, 2020

- Managed and maintained the company's income and expenditure account.
- Maintained a well structured book of account for the company.
- Filled and managed VAT returns for the company.
- Reconciled the company's cash book with the bank statement

EMINENT SUPERMARKET, IBADAN

Oyo-State

Position: Account Manager

Jul, 2019 - Nov, 2019

- Maintained records of receipts and payments.
- Processed customers' transaction and issuance of appropriate changes.
- Ensured accuracy of cash receipts and checking for counterfeit.
- Managed and sanctioned collections of items that are meant for warehouse.
- Created a friendly environment and greeting the customer with a welcoming smile.
- Involved in reconciliation of physical stock in the system.
- Involved in the restocking of goods.

NYSC, COMMUNITY SECONDARY SCHOOL, IBADAN

Oyo-State

Position: Auxiliary Teacher/Corps Member

Jun, 2019 – Oct, 2019

- Served as the Assistant Class Teacher for a Senior Class, a role that improved my people management skill
- Taught Economics to Senior Classes
- Conducted tests for students.

NYSC, BENIN ELECTRICITY DISTRIBUTION COMPANY, BENIN

Edo-State

Position: Enumeration Officer

Dec, 2018 – May, 2019

- Gathered records of customer's meter on power consumption, a role that aided my customer connection
- Involved in capturing customers' information into company's database developing the ability to work in teams
- Assisted in Mapping and Property Indexing.
- Enumerated all company's assets, tag and label for ease identification.

AWOJOBI LO & CO CHARTERED ACCOUNTANT

Lagos-State

Position: Intern Mar, 2018 – May, 2018

• Reconciled clients' bank statement with their cash book

- Updated clients' accounts
- Marketing of brand product

EDUCATION

OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY, IFE

B.Sc. Accounting [Second Class Upper Honours]

Osun State Feb. 2018

FEDERAL GOVERNMENT GIRLS' COLLEGE

West African Senior Secondary School Certificate (WASSCE)

Osun-State 2012

CERTIFICATION

Associate Chartered Accountant, Institute of Chartered Accountant of Nigeria.

National Youth Service Corps.

Certificate of Participation on International Financial Reporting Standard.

Certificate of Participation in the Nigerian Students' Economic and Leadership Summit.

Certificate of Participation on ICT training for fresh undergraduate.

2015

Certificate of meritorious service for the FYB committee of Accounting dept. 2016/2017 academic session.

SKILLS

- Proficient in Microsoft Office suites.
- Intermediate proficiency in Sage and Quickbook
- Ability to manage time and prioritize workload to ensure efficient delivery of tasks.
- Effective communication skill
- Excellent team building skills.
- High level of attention to detail.
- Ability to work with little or no supervision
- Excellent typing skill

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

- Calculating
- Typing
- Reading
- Writing
- Surfing the net.

REFEREES

Available on request